runt-of-the-web.com 2019-07-23

# Runt Of The Web's Privacy Policy

Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:

Our Commitment To Privacy  
Third Party Advertising & Analytics  
The Information We Collect  
How We Use Information  
Our Commitment To Data Security  
How To Access Or Correct Your Information  
How To Contact Us

Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Third Party Advertising & Analytics

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

We may allow third parties to place and read their own cookies, web beacons, Local Shared Objects, and other technologies to collect information through the Services. For example, our third-party service providers may use these technologies to collect information (i) that helps us with traffic measurement, research, and analytics, and (ii) that is used to serve advertisements on our Services and across the Internet tailored to your apparent interests. The information collected and stored by third parties remains subject to their policies and practices, including whether they continue to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices on what is visible to others on third-party services.

We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google. The cookies and other technologies used by Google may collect Personal Information, but Runt of hte Web does not use Google Analytics to gather information that personally identifies you. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to [Google’s privacy policies](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites). You may exercise choices regarding the use of cookies from Google Analytics by going to https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout or downloading the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.

You may choose whether to receive interest-based advertising by submitting opt-outs. Some of the advertisers and service providers that perform advertising-related services for us and our partners may participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. To learn more about how you can exercise certain choices regarding Interest-based Advertising, visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices, and http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices for information on the DAA’s opt-out program for mobile apps. Some of these companies may also be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). To learn more about the NAI and your opt-out options for their members, see http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.

Our advertising partners include:

AppNexus | [Privacy Policy](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy) | [Opt-out from data use](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy#choices)  
Google | [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) | [Opt-out from data use](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated)  
OpenX | [Privacy Policy](https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/) | [Opt-out from data use](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)  
Sonobi | [Privacy Policy](http://sonobi.com/privacy-policy/) | [Opt-out from data use](http://sonobi.com/privacy-policy/)  
Teads | [Privacy Policy](https://teads.tv/privacy-policy/) | [Opt-out from data use](https://teads.tv/privacy-policy/#6)  
TripleLift | [Privacy Policy](https://triplelift.com/privacy/) | [Opt-out from data use](https://triplelift.com/privacy/)

Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to the websites with which the user communicates. Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. Because there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals, Runt of the Web currently does not take action in response to these signals. For more information on “do-not-track,” visit http://www.allaboutdnt.com.

The Information We Collect:

We collect no information at Runt-of-the-Web.com.

The Way We Use Information:

We do not use the information provided by users in any manner.

Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

We do not access or collect any of your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at pbhnetwork@gmail.com.
